[Music]
instead of forget just like have it
there i'm just gonna sweep him
that's right all right so i haven't done
any videos in a while where i literally
took a hundred and two dollars or two
dollars
a hundred and two dollars to about three
thousand in about i think two three
weeks pop up the screenshot right here
of the account that i have i'm literally
gonna break down every single trade that
i took and how much i risk per trade
right you guys literally saw me do this
because i gave you guys the investor
password i'll send i'll pop up some
screenshots here of like me posting it
on my instagram story literally popped
it up on the podcast with q i literally
gave you guys the investor password to
all of these trades so i'm gonna do a
breakdown on every single trade that i
took how much i risk and kind of how i
went about it um when i was taking the
trade but i actually am splitting this
account in half and i'm giving it away
to my top student pop-up picture
fernando
fernando this guy's a threat to the
markets this guy literally flipped
1500 bucks to about 3 000 i think in
like three four days and he's actually
up right now seven percent on this
challenge and i think two weeks and i
have for my 30 day bootcamp i think like
four other traders no three traders that
are funded and then the other trader
just passed two 200k accounts so about
to be funded 400k um so that's crazy so
i'm gonna make fernando go up against a
random trader so obviously stay tuned
for that i'll make a series out of it um
and then obviously they're gonna go
ahead and do a little uh profit split
basically gonna decide what they're
gonna do but i'm thinking of doing
another boot camp i haven't done a boot
camp in two months so i do a webinar
every single week with every uh you know
i have a the community from the boot
camp it's not just 30 days and then i'm
out i don't like doing that i literally
do webinar every single week you know we
chatted up in the group chat like i
literally build a community and i give
you guys a buddy so we all kind of trade
together when we hop on the zooms so i'm
thinking of doing another boot camp
probably one last time before the year
ends maybe kind of debating on it
because i like doing it with maybe
either 15 or 20 people max
um so if you guys want to join the
waiting list the witness is going to be
below i could get about 10 to 15 people
to join then i might do it but the only
way to obviously get access to it is
with a waiting list so the link is in
the description
um with that being said we're going to
get into the video on where i'm going to
show you guys how i flip the account
from 100 to 3 000 full transparency on
everything and um
oh yeah you guys asked for it
instead of your merch so i haven't like
literally we got a bunch of different
you know
sizes i mean it's a very simple like
concept you guys already know if you're
not setting and forgetting like what
you're doing right and like bro just a
quarter like touch it touch it touch it
like you touch it crap crap
hey yo
you told me to touch it yeah no yeah
real sure like this is not like no loose
quality but this quality is actually
like pretty fit you can tell us like
everywhere um so this is probably going
to drop within a week i literally got a
couple hundred shirts and i already have
like my dreams are going crazy so i know
this is gonna go out fast um but with
that being said if you guys want to sign
up for the boot camp make sure to click
the link below and let's get into the
video all right what's up guys so now
that we're here let's go over every
single trade that i took so let's pop up
a screenshot of the trades
right here right so we're gonna start
off with usd cad
right so usd cad i don't remember if i
actually sent this trade in the signal
group because like i'm gonna be honest
i'm not gonna send every single like
trade that i'm gonna take an account
that i'm basically going full leverage
every single trade right i probably send
i want to say 75
of the trades in this account in the
chat the majority of the winners
obviously and you guys already know i
have this stupid sniper scalper in my
chat that like trades during london and
this man doesn't miss like i'm telling
you this guy hits every single night for
at least a one to three so when i don't
send the trade obviously because i'm a
swing trader my trades take a little bit
more time and then if i don't know he's
obviously selling at london so you're
getting a two in one package literally
with my segment chat if you guys want to
know more about the signal chat the link
in the description below
with that being said
my first cell right so my first cell as
you guys can see here was on usd cad on
4 26 which is obviously april 26th so i
can already see kind of why i sold this
um me personally uh it wasn't an ideal
cell it's probably a little bit rushed
as you can tell here we are obviously
going bullish we were doing higher highs
and higher lows so ideally i would have
wanted to sell at the break of this
neckline right here as you can tell we
kind of did a double bottom
and we're obviously bullish so i was
probably looking for this to break this
structure point here and go to the
downside but obviously i was going
against the trend clearly we were
bullish on the one hour i'm sure we go
out to the four hour we can see it here
when we bring it up
um where is it right around
here right right around here yeah so we
were definitely bullish um you can see
here we have high higher low higher high
higher low so literally sold at a higher
low but i was probably being a little
bit impatient i probably just wanted to
get the trade out of the way and i just
wanted to try to maybe get this counter
trend trade and to reach us to this zone
to then maybe buy was definitely a
little bit force uh forced trade on on
my end right so when it comes to risk on
this trade i probably just kind of like
to get involved in the trade i threw a
little 0.06 just to kind of get started
there's really no risk um that i kind of
calculated i obviously took a trade that
i wanted to take but it wasn't anything
like oh i'm going 100
all right trade number two on the same
day 426 was aud jpy cell right so as you
guys can see here we are obviously
let's see here on the daily down this is
annoying how it gets lost um
somewhere around here
all right right around right here
right around here right so we're
obviously bears as you can see we have a
higher high higher low higher high
higher low and then boom we broke this
bullish structure right here heading
obviously to the upside so we could kind
of set an area of interest around here
like this so once the daily breaks the
area of interest we're looking for the
retest of that area as you guys can see
here 426 is when we took the other trade
this is where i would go down to kind of
like the four hour and then i believe i
got my entry right around this zone
right here once it came back up and then
basically retested this resistance
support being used as resistance i can
find my entry signal a little bit around
here let me actually check the tray so
my entry signal was around
91928 so 91928
[Music]
91928 all right so yeah my entry signal
was right around here which is ideal
because as you can see yeah it was
definitely right here because it was
when we were getting the potential
left head and then the right shoulder so
obviously that's a reversal pattern
where at your area of interest on the
daily time frame that you're obviously
looking to take once we retested this
first area my risk was a little bit
higher than the first one just because i
liked how we were basically retesting
that daily structure so obviously moving
on our the next trade we took is um back
on usd cad you'll see cad this is
probably like the first win that puts me
on top like once you win the first trade
that for me is just something where it's
just like all right bet like like you
know we're doing something right like
clearly we're on the money right so the
next trade it was a buy on usd cad so
what i kind of explained to you guys
like react and adapt is probably like
one of the most important things because
i was looking for a sell here on the
27th i mean on the 26th and then on the
27th i actually bought so i'm sure i can
point out my entry signal was 127
900 so perfect so literally where i was
looking to sell where i basically took
the loss um on this push right here
straight into the support i then bought
so this is basically i probably got it
in a little too late on the first one so
then i bought uh on this support here as
you guys can tell we're bullish we have
the higher high higher low we have the
double bottom and then my entry signal
my my entry was literally
127 900 exactly right here after this
bullish engulfing on the one hour and
i'm sure if i go down to the lower time
frames we have a better entry signal but
i just kind of don't want to lose the
chart um so obviously like i said react
and adapt we were looking for a little
counter train the counter trend trade to
sell didn't play out and then we get the
obviously other trade once you continue
with the trade right so that's a that's
a quick example of three trades of how
when you go against the trend and then
you lose and then the other two we go
with the trend and you win so that's
something definitely you want to write
down the trend is your friend it's very
very overlooked all right guys so our
next trade would be aud usd which was
our next big winner which i'm looking at
right now for 700 bucks so i think right
around that time we were probably
already like um but it'd be like almost
a thousand dollars right so
you literally need like two three trades
to kind of do this which is pretty crazy
right this trade i mean if you can't see
it already you got to go check out my
other videos or you guys just have to
like you know look up basic uh break up
structure as you can see here we were
obviously bearish we were heading to the
downside then the structure shifted
bullish what did we do here we shifted
the structure and now bearish again and
guess what we literally came back to
then retest the previous neckline from
this whammy double top or something like
that i know the candlestick bible has
the name as you can see here we then
have the perfect retest of the neckline
retest of structure structure structure
then you get your beautiful like i'm
talking about beautiful entry signal
right here for a
one hour bearish engulfing and then you
obviously said i forgot to trade all the
way down i actually had my take profit i
actually remember this one because i was
breaking it down with the signals my
take profit was right here was at this
previous structure level but i'm like
all right cool if this candle engulfs
i'm going to keep trailing my stops to
the downside i'm going to keep moving
along with it and then until i don't get
a bullish engulfing reversal i don't
close the trade so obviously we rode the
trade all the way down here and then i
saw this trade kind of like flickering
to the upside and i saw um like
rejection rejecting the zone and i was
scared that i was going to basically
come back into this level either retest
the ema or even make come back into this
level and do a double top and then take
me all the way down so i'm like you know
what i just take my profits here i'm
already up almost a thousand on the
account so i'm already about to be 10x
on the account so i'm like you know what
we'll take that and then we'll run with
it so this is definitely one of the
trades that put me on top but again goes
back with the basics the trend is your
friend we are heading to the downside as
you can see we're obviously doing very
structure here
why are you trying to buy these
pullbacks like what a lot of people
would do is let's say that they would
miss this sell right here so let's say
the trade would be all the way already
down here they're like oh all right bet
now it's going to have the retracement
and sell again so now here what they
would do is they would want to buy just
because they see a bullish engulfing but
no they're not taken into consideration
like bro you're buying right into a
structure point like literally trying to
jump like let's say you're six feet tall
i am not six feet tall but let's say i
was six feet tall you're literally
trying to jump to a roof that is six
feet one inches like you're gonna hit
your head that's not a high probability
setup so you're literally gonna hit your
head far to the ground that's exactly
what's happening here so what did i do
over here i sold because if we jump we
hit our head and then we fall down
that's what you want to do it's
obviously the simplest example that i
can put all right so our next trade is
here on gbp chf and this is a classic
trade where i feel like a lot of traders
would have gotten fomo and their
emotions would have literally like
killed them right why because
obviously beautiful trade you can see
here the trend same exact example you
guys are going to know a lot of these
trades look the same and this is the key
to my strategy and everything i teach in
the signals and the boot camps like bro
you don't need this not rocket science
you literally just got to get the
strategy the strategy and it's just
rinse and repeat right so you have here
obviously lower low you have the bare
structure now we go bullish you see
we're making higher highs and higher
lows so i bought at this level literally
perfectly 29.099
retesting the ema retesting structure i
can point out to hear a very simple
level of
support and resistance you see we have
support support resistance resistance
support support retesting the ema
and i'm not gonna lie i was probably a
little bit greedy because i wanted my
take profit to be 120 300 on the dot
like i wanted to hit that round
psychological hit these structure points
here
as you can tell price came up i was up
about
three percent obviously in this account
i don't go for percentage i look i go
for more just like flipping it for more
like the dollar amount and as you can
tell price literally came back and then
took me out of breakeven so once we had
like this bearish momentum here i was
like all right cool if we kind of break
under my entry i'm just going to close
the trade right i did so i asked what
kind of happened here i closed it um
profits were well it wasn't really a
profit it was a loss for 200 bucks so i
that was just more of like the
commission that i got charged and kind
of like just being in the trade the
whole entire time because as you can
tell i entered the trade on the second
commissioner rolled over to the third so
um you know that's just part part of the
game but obviously the trade did end up
playing out but this is where i can see
how a lot of people could be close to
the take profit and then get stopped out
of break even and not jump back in how i
did because of fomo or because of just
greed and their psychology is all over
whack and then they try to like you know
buy and then they get stuck and all this
and end up you know blowing their
account because they're like now trading
with emotion because you missed out on
the trade that you planned out perfectly
you just got wicked out of break even
and then your emotions go over your but
that's why you got to stick to your
psychology you got to stick to the plan
so now that i'm actually looking at this
trade right now adjpy which i actually
bought
ideally this is a terrible buy like
according to my strategy i should have
not bought this but it's actually pretty
interesting kind of going back like this
and looking at my trades i don't really
do this often but as you can tell here
yes we are obviously bullish the
structure is bullish
but notice how i bought at a resistance
i literally bought at a level that is
resistance support support right well i
don't think i actually bought right at
the resistance i'm sure i bought here on
the lower time frames once we broke
above but ideally i would want to have
taken a trade like this i would have
want to have bought within here so the
fact that i bought in here there was
something probably going on i probably
was just like you know [__] it let's
just take a trade versus certain amount
very interesting um kind of looking back
at this now my entry was around
around this zone here so i was
definitely expecting it to break out
maybe i kind of read some fundamentals
or was i looking at the overall bigger
picture
um yeah still doesn't really make sense
for me to have bought here so i'm a
little intrigued on why that happened um
maybe i was breaking it down with some
of the students but very interesting i
should have not taken this by here but
you know luckily it obviously ended up
playing out because as you can see we
were
bullish on the four hour but we are
buying at a resistance so that would
have not been the ideal setup so i'm
just gonna go to the last trade which is
aud usd which is like the big winner
basically the thousand dollar winner
which is the one that kind of sealed the
deal in a way um which was the cell that
i got here which is i want to say
another very textbook trade as you guys
can tell here this is a beautiful
beautiful beautiful beautiful reversal
pattern i remember like i even i posted
this all over instagram like on my story
like guys we literally have here bullish
structure you see how it's heading to
the upside
you have the slowdown you like literally
see price rejecting this level this
level is literally used as resistance
literally used as resistance as support
and i'm sure we look more left that is
used as more support and resistance
right as you can see so what happens
once we came into this zone right here
is we then had this literal shift like
you can see the structure change like
you can see we are headed to the upside
just by the ema alone you can see how
we're headed to the upside and then we
literally reverse to the downside so not
only do we shift the structure but now
we were under our ema and this is
basically where i entered my cells right
here i remember this perfectly why did i
enter the cell because we are retesting
um
support now being used as resistance
bullet structure has now shifted bearish
structure rejection from super strong
resistance under the ema and then you
have your bearish engulfing rejection
from around psychological level like it
just doesn't get any better than that
like super simple right so it's kind of
like a little bit of a rundown of every
single trade that i sent um i could do a
little bit more in detail but obviously
i don't know i don't know how
um well you guys are kind of
understanding this i know my last video
that i uploaded you guys said it was
crystal perfect clear so that's why i'm
kind of little taking a little bit more
into depth here so if you guys want to
see even more advanced um
join the waiting list in the boot camp
that's where i literally reveal
everything that i do um if i do end up
getting like around like the people that
i that i that i want to get because i
only work with a selective amount of
people i like working with serious
people because i throw you into a chat
with other serious traders so um
yeah just stay tuned for that make sure
to like comment and subscribe new videos
every tuesdays and fridays podcast and
uh podcast every friday so if you guys
want to see more videos like this make
sure to uh drop a comment and if you
guys maybe want to see like a part two
to this i know i have some part two's
pending from the ema from the last video
and then if you know you guys kind of
like this one i want to see more in
depth um yeah and stay tuned stay tuned
for this friday's podcast it's going to
be pretty interesting so thank you guys
for watching all the way to the end and
i hope you guys found great value in
this and i'll see you guys in the next